ajnabii.com 2013-04-30

# Privacy Policy

> **Ajnabii.com “Privacy Policy”**

We take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

> **Routine Information Collection**

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.

> **Cookies and Web Beacons**

Where necessary, this site uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.  
****

> **  
> C** **ontrolling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

> **Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. [Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some third-party advertisers used by Google may use a different cookie. You may opt out of most third-party advertising cookies by [following this link  and visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), or [by visiting this Consumers page to opt out of all advertising cookies](http://www.evidon.com/consumers/profile_manager#tab3).

> **External Links**

Ajnabii.com  contains links of other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites we link to. We do make an effort to avoid linking to known “adult” and “porn” sites. Ajnabii.com  is a clean and safe secure web site.

> **Disclaimer**

If you see any Copyrighted Images, videos, Content, Or any  Contents related to you and want to remove it. Please [Contact Us](http://ajnabii.com/contact-us)  with the details, we will remove within 48 hours.

> **Changes To Our Privacy Policy**

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site.
